const data = [
    {
        question: "Who invented the JavaScript and in what year",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Brendan Eich in 1997",
            "Brendan Rich in 1995",
            "Hakon Wium Lie in 1997",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Bredan Eich in 1995",
    },

    {
        question: "The JavaScript was first Developed for?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Netscape 1.0",
            "ECMA 264 Standard",
            "SQL",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Netscape 2.0",
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following is true about JavaScript",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "JavaScript Specifies the Layout of a Web page",
            "JavaScript Defines the content of a webpage",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The behaviour of a Webpage is defined by JavaScript",
    },

    {
        question: "All the following is true about JavaScript except",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Multiple JavaScripts can be placed in a Single HTML document",
            "A JavaScript function is a block of JavaScript code, that can be executed when for",
            "The behaviour of a Webpage is defined by JavaScript",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript defines the Style of a Webpage",
    },

    {
        question: "Another name for Invoke in JavaScript is_______",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "getElementByClassname",
            "OnClick",
            "getElementById",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Call",
    },
    
    {
        question: "All of the following are method of referencing Extenal JavaScript except",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "file Path",
            "full URL",
            "Without and Path",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Cascading",
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following is used for Testing purposes in JavaScript",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "getElementById",
            "document.test()",
            "console.log()",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "document.write()",
    },
    
    {
        question: "We write into a browser Console Using what command",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "document.write()",
            "console.write()",
            "windows.alert()",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "console.log()",
    },

    {
        question: "JavaScript Statements are composed of the following except:",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Expression",
            "values",
            "operators",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above",
    },

    {
        question: "ariables declared with the var are _______",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Localalized Variables",
            "Delocalalized Variables",
            "operators",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Global Variables",
    },
]

export default data;